javacodegeeks.com 2019-08-24

# Privacy Policy | Java Code Geeks - 2019

Exelixis Media P.C. (holding company of Java Code Geeks) is committed to protecting your privacy. The following privacy policy describes the ways in which Exelixis Media P.C. gathers and shares your personal information as well as how you can access and update this information. Exelixis Media P.C. reserves the right to update this privacy policy at any time. Any modifications to our privacy policy will be reflected on Java Code Geeks (Site). The revised policy will appear on our Site with the date of last revision. Your continued use of the Site following such revisions will be conclusively deemed acceptance of any changes to these Terms.

### The types of information we collect

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Because we derive revenue mainly from advertising, collecting information is essential to keeping our services affordable to users. As further described below, by clicking on advertisements on the Site and taking advantage of sponsored content on the Site, you consent to the delivery of the personal information gathered by Exelixis Media P.C. to Exelixis Media’s advertisers and sponsors. We collect personally identifiable information, which includes, among others, name and e-mail address.

### Collection of Personal Data

When inquiring about use of or subscribing to or otherwise using the Site, you may provide certain personally identifiable information necessary for use of the Site and for communicating with you. The data collected includes information about you that can be used to contact or identify you, and information related to your use or potential use of Site (collectively, “Personal Information”). Personal Information that we collect may include without limitation name, email address, organization, job title, and phone number. Within our Site, if you interact with other users, the Site may share additional information with such other users. The additional information you share by participating in these types of communications is your choice and responsibility and the privacy of such information cannot be guaranteed. Similarly, information you share through messaging within our Site is solely your responsibility. We will maintain your personal data so long as your account is active.

### Cookies

Exelixis Media P.C. and our advertisers may send “cookies” to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie can’t read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies as part of the Site to store your viewing preferences on the Site and, at your choosing, to store your login information so that once you have logged in you do not need to repeat the login process. We also use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. Furthermore we use a cookie to count Web page accesses and gather general statistical information. We may also allow our third party partners to place their own cookies on your computer in order to serve you with relevant advertising online. This third party cookie may transfer non-personally identifiable information to the third party partner in order for them to track your activity when you visit our Sites and on sites outside the Exelixis Media P.C. network for purposes of serving you ads on topics in which you have a demonstrated interest based on your clickstream data; please note that we do not share member information with these third parties and we can only access cookies that we set on your computer, not the cookies sent to you by other companies. Also, when you leave the Exelixis Media P.C. network of Sites by clicking on sponsored content or advertising, these third parties may place cookies or clear GIFs on your computer. This Privacy Policy does not govern the use and disclosure of any information collected by third parties, such as through cookies or clear GIFs, when you visit their web sites or by third parties regarding your clickstream activity on sites other than Exelixis Media P.C. network of Sites. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Site, but your ability to use some areas of our Site will be limited.

### Pixel Tags

Exelixis Media P.C., its third party service providers and advertisers may use single-pixel gif images, sometimes referred to as pixel tags, web bugs or web beacons, to count Web page accesses and gather some general statistical information. We may use pixel tags to improve our understanding of site traffic, visitor behavior, and response to promotional campaigns, as a supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement. Pixel tags are sometimes used in conjunction with small Javascript-based applications, also for the purpose of traffic measurement. Exelixis Media P.C. does not gather personal information through the use of these images. Our advertisers and third party providers may use single-pixel gifs that can track personal information from cookies that may have been previously placed on a user’s computer. You can disable pixel tags by changing your browser settings to omit images and disable Javascript; or there are commercial software packages available that can omit pixel tags and most advertisements. Exelixis Media P.C. uses Google Analytics to measure site traffic, visitor behavior, and to improve delivery of services. To understand the information shared with Google, how it is processed, and how you can control the information collected by Google on the Site, visit <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>.

### How We Use Your Personal Information

We do not sell, rent, use or share your personal information with others except as indicated in this Privacy Policy.

#### Personally Identifiable Information

We use your personally identifiable information for the following purposes:

  * To provide the Site and associated content and services e.g. the Site membership
  * To complete information for you including your name, signature, and profile picture when you post content to the Site
  * To support, improve, maintain and update the Site
  * To communicate information to you that you have requested, such us e-mail newsletters and/or third party announcements
  * For our marketing, research and development purposes
  * For other purposes specified in this Privacy Policy or at the time information is requested from you

Comments or questions sent to us using email or other messaging tools will be shared with our staff that is most likely to be able to address your concerns. We may archive your messages once we have provided you with a response. If we find your personal question valuable to community discussion, we reserve the right to post your question on the Site, after using reasonable efforts to remove any names or personal identification. Please note that email communications will not necessarily be secure; accordingly, you should not include sensitive information in email correspondence with us.

In order to access third party content on the Site such as whitepapers, product downloads or any other content asset provided by a third party content provider, users need to update their profile to the Site. The profile information you provide may be shared with the content provider for the sole purpose of contacting you to assess your interest in its products and services. Exelixis Media P.C.  **will not** disclose your personal information to any third parties, except to its third party content providers whose information you have chosen to access. **If you do not want this information disclosed to a Content Provider, do not view the Third Party Content.** Third party content will be made clearly distinguishable on the Site.

Exelixis Media P.C. may also disclose Personal Information:

  * When we have your permission to do so
  * To companies who work for Exelixis Media P.C. to provide one or more parts of the Site or that provide related administrative functions (such as support Sites and analytics). These third parties may have access to your personal information; if they do, this access is only so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with a legal process or law, or to respond to a subpoena, court order, or government request for information, (2) enforce Terms of Service and/or other agreements between you and Exelixis Meida P.C., (3) respond to claims that any content on the Site violates the rights of third parties, or that otherwise arise from your use of the Site, or (4) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Exelixis Media P.C., its users, or the public
  * When required or permitted to do so by law for public safety. Disclosures may be made to protect you from a serious threat to your health or safety or to protect the health or safety of another person

##### Security

We use reasonable precautions to protect the personal information you disclose from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure. We only release this information to third parties we believe share our commitment to privacy.

##### Aggregate Information

We may aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional, and other purposes. We do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

#### Anonymous Information

In addition to personal information, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically captured when you visit the Site. This information includes the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site, occasional geographic data, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. We also may use your IP address to determine the organization that you are affiliated with. None of this information is personally identifiable. This anonymous information is used to help improve the Site, analyze trends, and administer the Site. We may monitor your interactions with the Site, such as what pages you visit, what content you review, and what comments you make, and maintain this information with your Site profile.

### Your Rights

You may withdraw your consent for disclosure of your Personal Information to sponsors of third-party content by providing notice to Exelixis Media P.C. at the address or email address noted below. If you withdraw your consent, your account will either be suspended or removed, or you will be restricted from downloading such content. You have the right to access and edit, update or delete your personal information by logging onto the Site and accessing your account information. You may contact us with any questions or if you need assistance in updating or deleting your personal information. You can ask us for a copy of your personal data in machine readable form.

### Third Parties and Links

This Privacy Policy applies only to our Site. We may provide links to other information and sites that we believe may be of interest to our users. Their sites may collect or request personally identifiable information from you. You should review the privacy policy of these sites before providing such information, as these sites are not covered by our Privacy Policy. We cannot guarantee the standards of sites to which we link or be responsible for the contents, or privacy practices and policies, of these and other third-party sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every site you visit. Our Site may include social media features, including the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the “share this” button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Site. These features may collect your IP address, where you are using our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features and widgets are governed by the privacy policy of the company that created the feature.

### Access to Account

If you are a registered user of the Site, you can change your account information through your user profile page. You may need to supply certain information so that we can try to verify that you have authority to modify this information.

### Opt-Out

When you provide your email address to us, you agree to receive e-mails from Exelixis Media P.C.. You may opt-out of receiving certain marketing communications from us, by emailing us at the address or email address noted below. In addition, all marketing e-mails from Exelixis Media P.C. will provide you with the opportunity to unsubscribe from future marketing mailings. Even if you opt out of such mailings, however, we reserve the right to send you e-mail and other communications to disclose maintenance and other Site-related issues.

### Legal Requirements

We intend to protect your privacy to the fullest extent possible as described in this policy while also fulfilling our responsibility to uphold all applicable laws and regulations. Due to potential legal requirements and other possible circumstances, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed or accessed in ways not otherwise described in this policy. We may be compelled under law to disclose information to government or third parties under certain circumstances or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Further, we can, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose any information to law enforcement or other government officials that we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in compliance with the law and/or government requests.

### United States

The Site is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing the Site from outside the United States, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. The United States may not have the same data protection laws as your country. However, to the extent that Regulation (EU) 2016/679, the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) applies to you, Exelixis Media P.C. will comply with GDPR.

### Security Measures

We have implemented reasonable and industry standard security measures on the Site to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the personal information under our control. Additionally, we take reasonable steps to ensure that our third party business partners, including our hosting partners, provide sufficient protection for personal information. We will take reasonable efforts to maintain Personal Information in the area (e.g., country or continent) as specified by our Customer. We will promptly make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data. You acknowledge that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, and that we cannot guarantee absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Site, you may contact us.

### Privacy of Children

Children under age 16 are not permitted to use the Site. We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information on the Site from children under 16. If we become aware that a user of the Site is under the age 16 and has provided us with Personal Information, we may delete such information from our files and may deactivate the related account.

### In the Event of Merger, Sale or Bankruptcy

In the event that all or part of Exelixis Media P.C. is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, Exelixis Media P.C. may transfer or assign the personally identifiable information held by Exelixis Media P.C. as part of such merger, acquisition, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of Exelixis Media’s bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, Exelixis Media P.C. may not be able to control how personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

### Support

Users who are experiencing problems with our services or who have questions about how our services work can contact us by sending an email or write to:  
Exelixis Media P.C.  
18 Nafpaktias Str.  
Kesariani, 16121 Attica Greece  

If you believe you have not received an appropriate response from us regarding your question or complaint, you may contact the applicable supervisory authority below based on your residence:

      * EU Data Protection Authorities (DPAs)
      * Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC)

##### Update Date : 5-25-2018
